So…
所以…
Can you get your hands on that thing?
你有辦法拿到那個東西嗎？
Yes.
有
Well then…
那麼…
shall we begin?
差不多該開始了吧
After checking the history on the old phone,
搜尋舊手機的履歷後
I managed to get in touch with someone.
我聯絡上了一個人
Someone who used to work for Egoshi.
他曾在江越手下工作過
That's great.
很好
Let's keep digging.
就這樣繼續追查下去
Next,
另外呢
I want to find out if that thing from 12 years ago is still around.
不知道那個12年前的東西還在不在
They should have it close by.
應該會留在他手邊
Egoshi exploits people's weaknesses to manipulate them.
抓住他人的弱點，支配對方
That's the kind of person they are.
江越就是那種人
Can I…
關於這點…
trust you on this?
我願意相信你
Yes.
好
Excuse me.
那我走了
Welcome back.
回來啦
You didn't have to wait outside, you know.
其實你不用在外面等也沒關係啊
I could see that Mr. Hiyama was in.
因為我看到緋山先生來了
We were discussing the second instance.
我們在討論二審的事
What about you?
你呢？
What are you up to so late?
這麼晚來這裡做什麼？
I need to fax it by tonight.
今天晚上一定得傳真
Is that so?
這樣啊
Mr. Kurata.
倉田先生
Your charges include aiding a false accusation
你的罪名是
However…
但是…
you should be able to challenge the detention requirement.
你可以對羈押的 構成要件該當性提出質疑
And even argue for a rejection of the detention request.
甚至能夠聲請撤銷羈押
I…
我…
will work on your defense.
會當你的辯護人
Asuka.
飛鳥
I'm not saying this as your daughter.
並非是作為你的女兒
I'm saying this as an attorney.
我會以一名律師的身分為你辯護
I don't need one.
我不需要律師
I agree to this arrest.
這次被逮捕，我沒有任何意見
I admit my crime
我打算認罪
and will pay for it.
並且贖罪
You agree?
沒有意見？
Are you going to pay for all your crimes, then?
所以你打算背負所有罪行嗎？
Including the false accusation against Mr. Shimizu?
連志水先生的冤罪也一起？
Attorney Shinomiya,
紫之宮律師
I have nothing more to say to you.
我已經沒有話要說了
We're done here.
我們談完了
Did you know…
你知道嗎？
Attorney Shinomiya?
紫之宮律師
Even the best doctors
不論是多厲害的名醫
find it hard to operate on their own family.
幫自己的親人動手術會非常困難
When faced with an illness that afflicts their family,
這是因為面對侵蝕家人的疾病
they're forced to confront…
會徹底了解到…
their own powerlessness.
自己有多無力
If you want to help your father,
你若為父親著想
you should let…
他的辯護人
a cool-headed third party handle his defense.
請其他冷靜的人擔任比較好
A lot of things must have come as a shock to you.
你一定也受到了很大的打擊吧
You have…
我能理解…
my sympathies.
你的心情
Chief Prosecutor Datehara?
伊達原檢事正？
He's acquainted with Chief Kurata?
他認識倉田刑事部長嗎？
I'm not sure.
我不確定
But he seemed to know about me.
但是他也認得我
My father confessed to fabricating this incident.
我父親承認在這起案件中 他捏造了事實
But…
但是…
he still won't say anything about Mr. Shimizu's case.
關於志水先生的案件
Just maybe…
說不定…
Hiyama is involved in Mr. Shimizu's case as well.
緋山也跟志水先生的案件有關
Mr. Hiyama?
緋山先生嗎？
Last night,
其實昨天
Hiyama was actually at the office.
緋山有來事務所
Mr. Akizumi said they were discussing the second instance,
雖然明墨律師說他們在討論二審的事
but their conversation was completely unrelated.
但他們談的卻是完全不同的內容
It seems Mr. Akizumi
明墨律師他啊
is getting Hiyama to locate someone.
似乎要緋山幫忙找人
"If that thing from 12 years ago is still around."
“不知道那個 12年前的東西還在不在”
That's what I heard him say.
他還這樣說
If Mr. Shimizu…
如果志水先生
is truly falsely accused,
真的是被冤枉的
now that I know, I can't back down.
既然都知道了，我就無法退讓
I've been witnessing an innocent person
因為我一直看著
endure unimaginable suffering…
那些蒙受不白之冤的人
for so long.
承受著難以想像的痛苦
I want to uncover what my father is hiding.
我也想知道父親到底在隱瞞什麼
If there are people being harmed because of him…
如果有人因他而受到傷害…
I share the responsibility too.
那我也有責任
The decision.
主文
The accused is sentenced to one year in prison.
將被告判處有期徒刑一年
The execution of the sentence will be suspended for two years
自本判決確定之日起兩年內
from the day it becomes final.
暫緩執行刑罰
I cannot accept this.
我無法接受
I was set up!
我是被陷害的！
I'll appeal this case.
我要上訴
I want the process started now.
立刻辦理手續
About that…
關於那點…
Ms. Maki Sawahara?
你就是澤原麻希小姐吧？
Yes?
沒錯
I will secure an acquittal for you.
我會讓你獲判無罪
My name is Maki Sawahara.
我是澤原麻希
I used to be the vice editor-in-chief of Taiyo Weekly at Taiyo Publishing.
我以前是大洋出版社 《大洋周刊》的副主編
Remember the information leak incident at Taiyo Publishing?
你們還記得大洋出版社的 資料外洩事件吧？
It caused quite a commotion.
當時鬧得沸沸揚揚呢
There was awful slander on social media about it.
社群網站上的毀謗也很嚴重
As I recall, the culprit was the vice editor-in-chief…
我記得犯人是副主編…
Yes, that's the incident.
沒錯，就是那個事件
Last December, after inquiries by the group's employees,
去年12月因為集團員工提出的疑問
suspicions arose that the employees' private information was being leaked.
發現員工的個人資料可能已經外洩
Investigations revealed that 300,000 pieces of data had been leaked,
調查後發現公司的機密資料 以及客戶的資料
including the company's confidential and client information,
還有集團所有員工的個人資料等
as well as the personal information of all group employees.
總計30萬筆早已外洩
Based on circumstantial evidence,
警察從間接證據推斷
the police focused their investigation on an active employee,
是在職員工所為，展開調查
leading to Ms. Sawahara's arrest.
最後逮捕了澤原小姐
But I really didn't do it.
但真的不是我做的
I'm absolutely innocent.
對此我根本毫無印象
So we're defending a second instance.
是二審辯護的委託呢
Two key points led to the decision in the first instance.
一審被判有罪的原因主要有兩點
First, during the investigation into the information leak route,
其中一個是調查資料外洩的路徑後
they found Ms. Sawahara's ID was being used.
發現使用的是澤原小姐的帳號
I lost my company ID last year.
去年我的員工識別證不見了
I keep it in my bag's inside pocket, but I couldn't find it on my way home.
我平常都放在包包的內袋裡 但要回家時就找不到
So, it's likely the real culprit stole your ID and misused it.
所以是真凶偷了 你的識別證來盜用帳號
Apparently, the time the ID was used to access the information
我的帳號被登入的時間
was around 8 p.m. on December 5th, the same time my card was likely stolen.
似乎也是識別證被偷的 12月5日晚上八點左右
And the second point that led to the guilty verdict is this.
而被判有罪的原因是第二點
STARLIST, the list broker that the information was leaked to,
在澤原小姐的帳戶中發現了 超過三百萬圓的匯款
deposited over 3 million yen to Ms. Sawahara's account.
這筆錢來自收到外洩資料的 個資販賣業者，星簿公司
I never knew this company,
我根本不知道那間公司
and I didn't even notice this deposit until the police pointed it out.
連那筆錢也是警方告知後我才發現的
This also worked against you in the first instance.
這點似乎也讓你在一審中不利
If you had realized the deposit right away and inquired about it,
如果你馬上就發現這筆錢 向銀行確認的話
the circumstances may have been different.
結果可能會有所不同
What was STARLIST's response regarding the deposit?
匯款進去的星簿公司是怎麼說的？
According to Hiroki Tamura, STARLIST's former representative director,
根據前代表董事，田村浩紀的供述
the leaked information was placed on a USB drive and sent to them by mail.
外洩資料是被儲存在隨身碟中 郵寄到他們公司
So basically,
也就是說
the real culprit stole Ms. Sawahara's ID to extract inside information
真凶利用澤原小姐的帳號 竊取內部資料
and sent it to STARLIST.
再將其寄給星簿公司
Then, they arranged for the reward to go to Ms. Sawahara's account.
讓他們把酬勞匯給澤原小姐
That's right.
是的
And according to forensics, the envelope and USB that were sent
另外，鑑識結果發現 寄出的信封和隨身碟上
had Ms. Sawahara's fingerprints on them.
都有附著澤原小姐的指紋
They were quite meticulous.
準備得真是周到
But why did the real culprit try to pin the blame on you?
但是為什麼真凶要嫁禍給澤原小姐？
They wanted to bring her down.
是想陷害她吧
It has to be someone within the company.
會做這種事的一定是公司內部的人
Do you have any idea who it might be?
你對犯人是誰有頭緒嗎？
I can't say for certain,
我無法斷定
but I had a subordinate named Ueda who used to be my supervisor.
但我有一名叫上田的下屬 他原本是我的上司
A subordinate who was your former supervisor?
原本是上司的下屬？
I was promoted to vice editor-in-chief, ahead of Ueda, who was a copy editor.
我越過身為編輯部主任的上田 一口氣就升為副主編
That's amazing.
好厲害
Not really.
沒有這回事
If I weren't a woman, this transfer wouldn't have happened.
如果我不是女性 是不會升遷得這麼快的
Was it part of a push to promote women?
是因為任用女性的趨勢嗎？
Yes.
是的
During the personnel transfers in July last year,
在去年7月的人事異動時
many women got promoted.
女性員工陸續升職
When your positions are reversed, it does make things awkward.
立場逆轉的話，的確很尷尬呢
Ms. Sawahara, do you suspect Mr. Ueda is the culprit?
澤原小姐認為 那位上田先生是犯人嗎？
I don't have any evidence, but yes.
對，雖然我沒有證據
The country is promoting women's appointments,
任用女性明明是國家的政策
but some suffer because of it.
卻有人因此受苦
Isn't that irresponsible?
也太不負責了吧？
Not all companies are like that.
但也不是每間公司都那樣
But media companies are lagging behind,
媒體業有點跟不上時代
leading to incidents like this one.
所以才會像這次，發展成事件
I get it might be unpleasant to have a subordinate promoted over you.
下屬升遷得比自己快的確很不是滋味
But is that enough motive to do this?
不過會因此做得這麼狠嗎？
True.
的確如此
Internal information leaks have a limited pool of suspects.
外洩內部資料
All the evidence points to Ms. Sawahara,
證據說明了一切都是澤原小姐所為
to an unnatural degree.
到了不自然的地步
Usually, culprits try to hide their tracks to avoid suspicion.
一般來說，犯人會隱藏自己的罪行
And yet, her name, address, and deposit account were all out there.
但這次有名字、地址、匯款帳號 還有指紋
As if begging to be arrested.
就像在催人快進行逮捕
So, someone clearly framed Ms. Sawahara.
果然是這樣，是有人陷害澤原小姐
In a recent incident, the police presented false testimony.
本次證實了警方捏造證詞
There was a case where the prosecution replaced a test result as well.
以前也曾有檢察官改寫鑑定結果
What do you believe motivates these acts of misconduct?
你認為是什麼導致 這些違法行為發生的呢？
For those of us in the judicial system,
對我們這些司法人員來說
trials are a part of our job and lives.
審判是工作，也是日常生活
However, a trial holds the power to determine someone's fate.
但是一場審判 會大幅影響一個人的人生
We must never forget this simple fact.
絕對不能忘記這個理所當然的事實
Therefore, through my work as an attorney,
因此我今後會繼續進行辯護
I aim to keep many judicial officials on their toes.
藉此警告眾多司法相關人員
That interview was truly meaningful.
本次採訪非常有意義
Your perspective exposed the misconduct of the Chiba Police.
尤其是揭露千葉縣警 違法行為的著眼點
I was especially impressed by that.
令我深感佩服
I hope my story was adequate.
只要你們不嫌棄這種話題就好
Given the nature of your story, I'm sure it will elicit a strong response.
這次的內容應該會獲得很大的迴響
That's good.
那就好
Mr. Akizumi, I need to use the bathroom.
明墨律師，我去一下洗手間
Go ahead. It's over there.
來，在那邊
-Excuse me as well. -Of course.
-我也先失陪了 -好
May I take a look at your workspace?
我能夠稍微參觀一下 你的工作場所嗎？
Of course.
當然可以
By the way, I heard a trial the other day resulted in a guilty verdict.
話說回來，前陣子她被判有罪了呢
Wasn't the accused the former vice editor-in-chief here?
我記得她是這裡的前副主編？
I'm sorry for any disturbance that caused.
不好意思，驚擾你了
It's all right.
沒關係啦
I'm just curious because of my line of work.
身為律師，我有點興趣
Could you tell me more about it?
方便的話能告訴我
What kind of person was she?
她是什麼樣的人嗎？
I'm sorry!
抱歉！
No worries.
沒關係
Thank you.
謝謝
Well…
我想想
She was very hardworking and competent.
她非常熱衷於工作，很優秀
She'd do anything for a scoop.
只要是為了獨家新聞 感覺她什麼都願意做
But if she was so dedicated,
如此認真工作的人
what could have motivated her to leak information?
外洩資料又有什麼好處呢？
Especially after the struggles to become vice editor-in-chief.
明明都辛苦爬到副主編的位置了
Well, I'm not so sure about that.
這個嘛，我也不知道
I wonder if she was unhappy with her workplace.
她是不是對職場有什麼不滿呢？
To be honest, it seemed like she didn't get along with her subordinates.
老實說，她跟下屬處得不太好
I tried to intervene and offer advice,
我曾居中協調，也給過她建議
but once a relationship goes sour, it's hard to repair.
但只要發生這種事就很難解決呢
I see.
這樣啊
But with her arrest,
但也因為她被逮捕
you ended up becoming the vice editor-in-chief.
上田先生才能成為副主編
Weren't you secretly pleased?
其實你很開心吧？
What? No.
不，才沒有呢
Ms. Sawahara is claiming innocence.
澤原小姐主張自己無罪
If what she says is true,
如果她說的是真的
it implies the culprit is someone else.
真凶就另有其人
What?
什麼？
I'm her attorney, you see.
我是她的辯護律師
I'll see you again.
下次見囉
Ms. Sawahara, huh?
澤原小姐啊？
She was promoted to vice editor-in-chief,
你是說她被提拔為副主編
but couldn't deliver much, so her demotion was decided.
卻拿不出成果，將被降職的事？
They say she leaked the information out of spite.
聽說她是為了洩憤才外洩資料
I see.
原來如此
Mr. Ueda is a good man.
上田先生是個好人
Ms. Sawahara was the one snapping at him.
反而是澤原小姐對他抱有敵意
Yeah.
沒錯…
When she was working under Mr. Ueda,
上田先生還是她上司時
no matter how many times he'd tell her to drop something,
他曾說過好幾次 “不要再採訪那件事了”
she'd never obey him.
但是她完全不聽
I see.
原來如此
Thank you.
謝謝你們
-Good work.
-辛苦了
-Excuse me. -Yes?
-不好意思 -是
May I see the entry log for December 5th of last year?
我能看看去年 12月5日的入館紀錄嗎？
No, I'm afraid that's not possible.
不，有點困難耶
We can't share that with outsiders.
不能讓外部人員看
Is that so? Well then,
這樣啊，那麼…
I'll report your conduct during work.
我會向他們投訴你的執勤態度
Huh?
什麼？
Smoking isn't allowed anywhere on the premises, correct?
這裡全面禁菸吧？
Every time you use your ID card, your entries and exits are recorded.
只要一刷識別證就會留下進出紀錄
What if someone loses their ID?
如果識別證弄丟了呢？
We ask for another form of ID, contact their department head,
只要出示身分證明文件
Would you view that record as well?
要查看那些紀錄嗎？
Yes, please.
麻煩你了
TAIYO WEEKLY
（《大洋周刊》）
At the time of the incident,
事件發生時
there were a total of 79 people inside the building.
還留在公司裡的員工共有79名
Of which only two were from the Taiyo Weekly editorial department.
其中有2名《大洋周刊》 編輯部的員工
Ms. Sawahara and Mr. Ueda.
就是澤原小姐跟上田先生
-Excuse me. -Whoa.
不好意思
What's with all the stuff?
你怎麼提了那麼多東西？
Could you take a look at these?
請大家看看這些
These were issued before Ms. Sawahara became vice editor-in-chief.
這些是澤原小姐 成為副主編前發行的雜誌
These were issued after she assumed the position.
這些是澤原小姐成為副主編後發行的
And these were issued following Ms. Sawahara's arrest
這些則是澤原小姐被逮捕之後
and Mr. Ueda's promotion to vice editor-in-chief.
上田先生成為副主編後發行的雜誌
During the five months Ms. Sawahara was vice editor-in-chief,
在澤原小姐擔任副主編的五個月間
there was a series of special features.
製作了一系列的特輯
Do you mean this?
你是指這個嗎？
An exposé article on Tatsuya Kazaki, a Mineito Party Diet member.
關於民營黨議員 加崎達也的醜聞報導
"Suspected of having affairs with multiple women."
“被爆料疑似出軌多位女性”
And this one says,
這篇是說
"Partying with a major company head for several consecutive days."
“和大企業的社長連日開派對”
How foolish.
真蠢
Isn't Kazaki the State Minister of Justice?
加崎是法務副大臣對吧？
Yes, he's a Diet member from the opposing faction of Seiji Tomita.
是的，他是跟富田誠二 對立派系的議員
One of the two was speculated to be the next Minister of Justice.
大家都說他們其中之一 會是下一屆的法務大臣
But after Tomita's downfall, Kazaki is the only real candidate.
但富田失勢後 加崎就成為唯一的候選人了
Factions still exist, huh?
到現在還是有派系存在？
Some things never change.
他們真是學不乖
It seems Ms. Sawahara had been investigating Kazaki for years,
澤原小姐長年追查加崎
but Mr. Ueda kept rejecting her articles.
但上田先生一直拒絕刊登這些報導
When she became the vice editor-in-chief, she finally managed to publish them.
所以她成為副主編後 這些醜聞才終於浮上檯面
But…
然而…
After her arrest,
她被逮捕後
articles about Kazaki stopped completely.
就完全沒有刊載加崎的話題了
Kazaki's pieces received a lot of attention,
加崎的報導獲得民眾的熱烈迴響
and the number of copies sold was increasing during that period.
據說當時雜誌的發行量也上升了很多
But Mr. Ueda adamantly refused to publish them.
但是上田先生卻不刊登相關報導
Aren't you curious about the reason?
你們不好奇原因嗎？
You think Ueda and Kazaki are connected?
你是指他們之間有什麼關係嗎？
Yes.
是的
If you already know that much, it makes things easier.
既然你已經察覺到，事情就好辦了
Here you go.
來，給你
It's already set up.
已經設定好了
Huh?
什麼？
Taiyo Publishing?
大洋出版社？
I'm sorry!
抱歉！
No worries.
沒關係
She was very hardworking and competent.
她非常熱衷於工作，很優秀
A GPS tracker?
定位追蹤器？
You want me to follow Mr. Ueda with this?
是要我用這個來跟蹤上田先生？
Ueda has always been a political reporter,
上田原本就是 在政治方面很有一套的記者
covering many Diet members' scandals.
他至今為止揭露了許多議員的醜聞
But his stories have something in common.
但那些報導有個共通點
I notice many exposés on the Takemoto faction.
盡是跟竹本派有關的醜聞
The Takemoto faction is the opposing faction of Kazaki.
竹本派跟加崎的派系對立
Scandals involving the Takemoto faction, which benefit Kazaki…
時機也抓得剛剛好 都是對加崎有利的竹本派醜聞
were published at just the right times.
總是剛好被爆出來
So, is Kazaki Mr. Ueda's source?
難道上田先生的情報來源是加崎？
So in this incident, Ms. Sawahara was an obstacle
這麼一想，會有這事件是因為 對加崎跟上田先生來說
for both Kazaki and Mr. Ueda.
澤原小姐很礙事
The reason someone could leak information, even at the risk of getting caught,
之所以冒著被逮捕的風險 也要外洩資料
is most likely because they had a politician backing them.
是因為有政治家做後盾 這樣想就一點也不奇怪了
I also…
然後…
have a task for you, Ms. Shinomiya.
要請紫之宮小姐做事
Like I said, the police took the USB that was sent here
我就說收到的隨身碟 已經被警察拿走了啊
and seized all the company's computers.
公司的電腦也全都被扣押了
What about that one?
那台電腦呢？
That's my personal laptop.
這是我的私人電腦
May I borrow it?
能借一下嗎？
Are you kidding? Give me a break.
開什麼玩笑？饒了我吧
You're evading a hefty amount of taxes.
你逃漏了很多稅呢
If I send this to someone I know at the National Tax Agency,
如果我告訴認識的國稅局人員
he'll be thrilled.
對方一定會很開心的
He's a rising star there.
他可是國稅局的明日之星
The other day, there was a tax evasion involving Kamehara Constructions.
你知道前陣子的 龜原建設逃稅事件嗎？
He handled that one too.
那也是他查到的
Found it.
有了
They ended up paying hundreds of millions in additional taxes…
那次追徵的稅款是幾億圓呢？
-Hello? -Hey! W-Wait a minute!
-喂？ -等等，你等一下！
I'll ask you again.
我再問一次
May I…
那台電腦…
borrow that?
能借我一下嗎？
YUMEMIRAI FESTIVAL
-歡迎光臨…
Good for you!
真棒啊！
Oh, yeah?
是喔
Eat up!
盡量吃！
Here. It's good.
給你，很好吃哦
You're welcome.
-謝謝 -不客氣
Thank you so much!
你明明那麼忙，還常過來 太感謝你了
I need to thank you as well.
我才要感謝你呢
My heart feels cleansed when I come here.
每次來這裡我整個人都被淨化了
Spending so much time in the courtroom can be so depressing.
一直待在法庭裡會讓人心情鬱悶
I'm glad to hear you say that.
很高興聽你這麼說
Director, the children are calling you!
園長，孩子們在找你！
Coming! Excuse me.
好！那我走了
I'll take that.
我來拿
Good work, everyone!
大家辛苦了
You haven't eaten yet, right?
你們還沒吃飯吧？
Here.
請用
-Thank you.
-謝謝
Would you like one too?
你也吃吧
Well, well.
真令人意外
You know who's handling the second instance, right?
你知道二審的法官是誰吧？
You shouldn't make contact with me before the trial.
在開庭前和我見面不好吧？
Make contact?
什麼見面？
I just happened to be here.
我們只是剛好遇到而已
At a children's home?
在兒童養護設施裡？
Yes.
是啊
I've taken an interest in volunteer work lately.
我最近想當志工
Is that so?
是嗎？
Well, if you say so.
算了，就當作是那樣吧
What about you, Judge Seko?
瀨古判事，我才想問你
Why do volunteer work?
你是在這裡當志工嗎？
I face sad incidents every day.
我們不是每天都會見到 很多悲傷的事件嗎？
And behind them, there are suffering children.
案件的背後有受苦的孩子們
I want to be of some help to them.
即使只有一點點也好，我想幫助他們
No.
不對
That was just me being grandiose.
我剛剛說的只是場面話
I come here for myself.
我來這裡是為了自己
Spending time with innocent children
和這些天真無邪的孩子在一起
helps me dispel the negative energy I accumulate.
能消除我內心累積的邪氣
Impressive.
真了不起
No wonder you're rumored to be the future Supreme Court Justice.
真不愧是總有一天 會成為最高裁判事的人
Very funny.
講得太誇張了
I want to help Ms. Maki Sawahara.
我想幫助澤原麻希小姐
She's maintaining her innocence,
她主張自己無罪
insisting she was framed by someone.
說是被其他人陷害的
I read the documents from her first instance.
她第一審的資料，你看過了嗎？
I sympathize with her.
我很同情她
It feels like seeing my past self.
簡直就像是在看過去的自己
While the circumstances are very different now,
雖然現在的環境跟以前完全不同
it's still a difficult world for women to live in.
但是女性的處境仍然很艱辛
We have a lead on who might have set her up.
我知道是誰陷害她
Is that so?
這樣啊
We're currently investigating this man.
我正在調查那名男人
We should obtain the evidence we need soon.
馬上就會找到證據了
Judge!
判事！
The mayor has come to greet you.
市長來打招呼了
Settle the score…
你可要幫她…
for her.
洗刷冤屈啊
You can stop coming.
已經夠了，你不用再來了
I know you're not to blame.
我明白這不是你的錯
Shoichiro's arrest made me feel a little better.
正一郎被逮捕後 我的內心也好受一點了
Shoichiro…
正一郎他…
was only arrested for a different case.
只是因為其他事件被逮捕
Nothing has changed yet.
你的處境沒有任何改變
You…
你…
are innocent.
是清白的
I'll never give up.
我絕不放棄
I don't want you to endure any more frustration.
我不想再令你感到懊悔了
So, please.
所以拜託你
Join me…
請再跟我一同…
in this fight again.
並肩作戰
You're really stubborn.
你真的很難纏
I read in a book.
我在書上有讀到
Unless you have substantial new evidence,
如果沒有發現明確的新證據
it's hard to get a retrial.
就算聲請再審也很難被受理
I'll find one.
我會找到的
I promise…
我一定會…
to prove your innocence!
證明你是無罪的！
I'll come again.
我還會再來
This one, huh?
就是這個嗎？
Yes.
是的
When I asked Ms. Sawahara,
已經跟澤原小姐確認過了
she said this man was Kazaki's chief secretary.
他是加崎的第一祕書
Apparently, the two meet at a bar called Luna's Bar.
他們似乎常常在這間魯納茲酒吧見面
According to the bar staff, Kazaki himself shows up sometimes.
據店員所說，加崎本人偶而也會出現
Just as I suspected.
果然如此
And you?
你那邊呢？
Right.
是
After the arrest, Tamura shut down STARLIST
澤原小姐被逮捕後，田村就辦理停業
and deleted all accounts under the company's name.
電子郵件以及社群網站上
Email, social media accounts, everything.
星簿公司的所有帳號都被刪除了
But fortunately, even though they were removed from the internet,
但幸運的是 雖然網路上的資料被刪除了
the data still remained on his laptop.
但是電腦裡還留著
And after having all the data restored by an expert…
我請專家將其全數復原後發現…
Are you familiar with this?
你們知道這個嗎？
It's a social networking site called SCRE. CHAT.
這是名為“斯克雷通訊”的社群網站
I know. It's an overseas platform known for its strong privacy measures.
我知道，這是國外 隱密性很高的網站吧？
Users are untrackable.
據說不會暴露自己的身分
Right.
沒錯
Using SCRE. CHAT, Tamura was involved in many backdoor deals.
透過斯克雷通訊 田村進行了多筆地下交易
So I focused on the period before December 5th,
然後我將範圍縮小到
the day the information supposedly leaked.
資料外洩的12月5日之前
And I got an expert to identify the users
請人調查了所有來信詢問的帳戶身分
One of them turned out to be…
在寄件人中…
a Taiyo Publishing employee.
發現大洋出版社員工的名字
Ueda?
“上田”？
Two months before the incident,
上田在案發的兩個月前
Ueda was making several inquiries to STARLIST.
寄了好幾封詢問信給星簿公司
Feelers like how much information could be sold for,
問願意用多少錢購買什麼樣的情報
and whether any evidence would remain.
並確認是否會留下證據等
He did his research using social media.
先透過社群網站進行調查
And to make the actual crime look like Ms. Sawahara's doing,
然後為了將罪行嫁禍給澤原小姐
he used an old-fashioned way by sending USB by mail.
而選用寄隨身碟這種傳統的方法
It seems so.
對
We can use this as evidence, right?
這能作為證據吧？
We can.
可以
As you know, in the second instance,
如同大家所知道的
new evidence isn't typically admitted unless there's a justifiable reason
二審時如果沒有正當理由
that it couldn't be presented in the first instance.
原則上只承認一審時提出的
However, if it's crucial evidence that contributes to uncovering the truth,
但如果是能揭示新事實的重要證據
the court may accept it ex officio.
法官也許會採用
In this trial,
這次的審判
whether the judge will accept new evidence will play a key part.
最大的關鍵就是法官是否採用新證據
Judge Narumi Seko of the Third Criminal Department
二審的法官是第三刑事部的 瀨古成美判事
So, in this case, we need compelling and persuasive evidence
也就是說本案中 我們需要提出能令瀨古判事承認
that Judge Seko will have no choice but to accept.
且具有說服力的重要證據
Morio!
森尾！
Shinomiya.
是紫之宮啊
-Heading to the courtroom? -Yeah.
要開庭了嗎？
The witness examination for the food poisoning case starts at 10 a.m.
十點開始要詰問食物中毒事件的證人
Oh, that one.
是那個事件啊
Hey, do you have a moment after that?
我問你，結束後你有時間嗎？
Sure.
有啊
All rise.
起立
The court is now in session.
那麼，正式開庭
Evidence number 17
辯方請求證據第17號
consists of STARLIST's every email and social media exchange.
是星簿公司的所有電子郵件 以及社群網站上的互動
This proves that there were no inquiries from the accused.
能從中發現被告人 沒有寄信給星簿公司過
But that Mr. Ueda, the former subordinate of the accused,
另一方面，能證明被告人的前下屬
had been sending inquiries to STARLIST.
上田先生曾寄信詢問過星簿公司
Furthermore, evidence number 18 and 19 include a photo showing Mr. Ueda
接下來是…
meeting Diet member Tatsuya Kazaki's chief secretary at Luna's Bar
上田先生跟加崎達也議員的第一祕書
and a testimony by the staff, respectively.
以及酒吧店員的供述書
It shows that Mr. Kazaki has been providing information
這些證據能夠證明
Lastly, there's personal evidence.
最後是證人之證詞
It became clear that Mr. Ueda had been rejecting the accused's articles
上田先生長年以來
I'd like to back this up with testimony from a Taiyo Publishing employee,
關於這一點 如同請求調查證據狀上所載明的
as per the request for examination of the evidence.
能藉由大洋出版社員工的證言來證明
Through these pieces of evidence, the defense counsel aims
辯方藉由以上證據
to shed light on the accused's workplace dynamics and relationships.
已查明被告在公司內部的狀況 以及人際關係
Bearing on that, firstly,
因此主張
Secondly, we aim to demonstrate
第二點，被告人被他人陷害
that she was framed to appear as if she deliberately leaked information.
設計得像是她主動外洩資料
We would like to prove these two points.
辯方想證明以上兩點
Your Honor,
庭上
these pieces of evidence are new facts, not uncovered during the first instance.
這些證據都是第一審時 沒有發現的新事實
According to Article 382-2 of the Code of Criminal Procedure,
根據刑事訴訟法382條之2
these reasons are due to unavoidable circumstances.
符合“不得已之事由”
Moreover, this evidence is pivotal in proving the accused's innocence.
更重要的是這些是 能證明被告無罪的重要證據
For the pursuit of truth,
為了辨明真相
I implore you to make a judicious decision.
懇請庭上做出正確的判斷
I see.
原來如此
Prosecutor, what is your opinion?
檢方的意見呢？
Any of these pieces of evidence
這些證據
could have been requested during the first instance.
都是在一審時即可聲請調查之證據
I believe they cannot be accepted.
我認為不該採用
You have a point.
也有道理
Given the timing of their acquisition and the particulars to be examined,
考慮到取得證據的時期
What do you think?
檢方的意見呢？
I agree on that front.
關於這點，我明白了
Instead,
但是在那之前
I request permission to summon Mr. Kiichi Ueda,
雖然比預定行程早
the former subordinate of the accused, as a witness ahead of schedule.
上田基一先生作為證人出庭吧
You answered earlier that Attorney Akizumi visited your workplace the other day.
你剛剛說過
Can you elaborate on this encounter?
能請你描述當天的狀況嗎？
That day, we invited Attorney Akizumi to our company for an interview.
那天為了採訪明墨律師 我請他來到敝公司
However, after the interview,
但是採訪結束後
he began grilling me about the accused.
他問了我很多跟被告人有關的事
It felt as though he was treating me as the culprit,
他的言行簡直就像是在說我是犯人
and it greatly troubled me.
令我非常困惑
Did you notice anything after that?
在那之後，你有發現什麼事情嗎？
Yes.
有
That night when I got home,
那天晚上回到家之後
I found something unfamiliar in my bag.
我發現包包裡有一個我沒看過的東西
What was it?
是什麼呢？
It was small
是很小的物品
and seemed to be a plastic object.
像是塑膠塊
To clarify his statement,
為求供述明確
I will present evidence number 36 as requested by the prosecution.
檢方請求證據甲方第36號
Proceed.
我准許
Is this that plastic object?
像是塑膠塊的東西是這個嗎？
That's right.
是的
When I examined it,
經過調查
I discovered it was a small GPS tracker.
我發現那是小型定位系統追蹤器
And then what did you do?
接著你是如何應對的呢？
I deliberately acted as if I hadn't noticed it.
我故意假裝沒發現
And what was the outcome?
結果呢？
I observed that I was being followed by a man I recognized.
我發現有個眼熟的男人屢次跟蹤我
Followed?
你被跟蹤了？
And who was this man?
那個男人是？
The man over there,
就是坐在那裡的
Attorney Akamine.
赤峰律師
Your Honor, to clarify his statement,
庭上，為求供述明確
I would like to present evidence number 37 as requested by the prosecution.
檢方請求證據甲方第37號
Proceed.
我准許
It's hard to believe this is the conduct of one involved in the law.
沒想到法界人士竟然會做出這種事
Objection.
我有異議
This is all mere speculation.
這些都只是臆測
True.
說得也是
Prosecutor,
檢察官
shouldn't you first present evidence that this is the work of the defense counsel?
應該先提出證據證明 此為辯護人所為再進行詰問吧？
But Your Honor,
但是庭上
you are aware of the illegality of conducting a GPS-based investigation.
定位系統偵查的違法性就如你所知
Even if carried out by the defense counsel,
雖說是辯方所為
it could constitute a serious violation of rights.
既然有嚴重侵犯證人權利的可能性
Therefore, I cannot agree to admit this series of evidence.
檢方就難以承認這些證據
Defense counsel, how do you respond to the prosecutor's assertion?
辯護人，對檢察官剛剛的主張 你有什麼要反駁的嗎？
It is true that the photo in evidence number 18
證據辯方第18號等照片
were obtained through shadowing Mr. Ueda.
的確是跟蹤證人所拍到的
Your Honor, there is no need for me to present evidence.
庭上，用不著提出證據
The defense counsel has openly admitted to it.
辯方剛剛已經承認了
Such actions are unforgivable.
這種事不可原諒
However, a GPS-based pursuit, shadowing, and capturing on camera
但是沒有國家權力的一般民眾
by an ordinary citizen, rather than by the authorities,
利用定位系統跟蹤、尾隨，以及攝影
cannot be immediately deemed illegal.
都是正當辯護的一環 若民眾的行為合法
As long as they were part of a reasonable defense activity.
辯方的行動也不該直接被認定為違法
Moreover, Your Honor,
庭上，更重要的是
I urge you to understand this.
我希望你能理解
The pieces of evidence requested by the defense counsel in this trial
辯方本次請求的證據 都是為了證明被告的清白
are essential in proving the innocence of the accused.
每一項都是不可或缺的證據
Ms. Maki Sawahara is innocent.
澤原麻希小姐是無辜的
And to establish this fact,
為了證明這個事實
we insist that these pieces of evidence are crucial and worthy of acceptance.
辯方主張這些證據應被採用
That is enough.
明白了
I understand the arguments from both sides.
我知道雙方的主張了
Now, I shall deliver the court's final decision.
那麼，本庭將發表結論
All pieces of evidence requested by the defense counsel in this trial…
辯方本次請求的所有證據…
will not be accepted.
皆不採用
Your Honor, but these are--
庭上，但這些是…
Although they may be crucial as the defense counsel has claimed,
如同辯方所主張的 這些可能是重要的證據
they were obtained through a breach of personal rights,
但是侵犯個人的人權
Therefore, they cannot be accepted as evidence.
本庭無法採用
Accepting such evidence would set a precedent
若是採用了這些證據
enabling the general public to freely deploy GPS trackers
就等同於認同一般市民
and engage in shadowing and secretly capturing people on camera.
進行尾隨以及偷拍
This will pose a threat to people's privacy.
這將會威脅到國民的隱私
As a courtroom judge, it is my responsibility
身為法院的法官
Therefore, these pieces of evidence cannot be accepted.
因此我無法採用這些證據
I direct the defense counsel to adhere to trial procedures
請辯護人遵守審判程序
and present evidence obtained through lawful means.
提出用正當手段取得的證據
Is that clear?
沒問題吧？
-But Ms. Sawahara is-- -Even…
-但是澤原小姐她… -即使…
in defense of the accused,
是為了保護被告
one must not resort to shameful conduct as a legal professional.
身為法界人士，請遵守規定 不要做出這種可恥的行為
Today's trial is adjourned.
今天的審理就到此為止
All rise.
起立
During Maki Sawahara's second instance,
澤原麻希的第二審
it seems the defense's pieces of evidence were dismissed.
辯方所提出的證據似乎未被採用
Ueda caught on to being followed and turned the tables, huh?
發現有人在跟蹤，反將一軍？
Quite impressive.
還真厲害呢
Who gave him that idea?
是誰教的呢？
I didn't do anything.
不，我什麼都沒做
I believe Judge Seko made a just ruling.
這都是因為瀨古判事 做出了正確的判斷
Indeed.
說得也是
This is Judge Seko we're talking about.
畢竟是瀨古小姐
She's the epitome of a fair judge, after all.
她簡直就是法官的榜樣
She is.
是的
By the way…
怎麼了？
Do you admire her or something?
你憧憬她嗎？
Actually, we've been on friendly terms for a while now.
其實她從以前就對我很好
Oh, is that so?
是嗎？原來是這樣啊
Speaking of which, she mentioned you.
對了，她也有說過你的事
Did she?
是喔
I can't imagine she said anything nice. She's not exactly fond of me.
她說了我的壞話吧？畢竟她討厭我
Not at all.
不，沒這回事
It's always beneficial to have a good relationship with a judge.
算了，跟判事打好關係是件好事
Just one thing, Midorikawa.
但是啊，綠川
A word of caution.
我要給你一個忠告
Don't surpass me.
可別爬得比我還高啊
Mr. Datehara, huh?
伊達原先生嗎？
From where I stand, he's on a completely different level.
他對我來說是遙不可及的存在
The accomplished prosecutor
他升遷的速度非比尋常
who rose to the top at an extraordinary pace.
是個非常厲害的檢察官
Extraordinary?
非比尋常？
I mean, he's already the Chief Prosecutor at his age.
他還這麼年輕就成為檢事正了
Compared to others his age, he's unmatched.
就算跟同期相比，他也是出類拔萃
He used to handle high-profile cases left and right.
他以前到現場勘驗時 解決了許多著名案件
It's legendary now.
成為了傳說
High-profile cases? Like what?
例如哪個著名案件？
Remember the embezzlement case involving Nishi Chiba Construction?
像是那個西千葉建設侵占事件
We were still in school then, but it was all over the news.
當時我們還是學生 但是新聞報得很大對吧？
Mr. Datehara handled that too?
-那也是伊達原檢事正負責的？ -沒錯
He used to be in the Chiba office.
因為他以前在千葉地檢署
The company's management was using underlings
據說這事件是公司幹部使喚下屬
to embezzle a ton of money.
盜取了很多錢
And I think there were murders related to that.
我記得還有一宗殺人案 也跟這個事件有關
The Itoi family murders?
糸井家滅門案？
Yeah, that one.
對，就是那個
The Chief Prosecutor led the investigation and cracked it.
據說那個案件也是檢事正 在前線負責指揮並解決的
But the name of the prosecutor on record was different.
但是承辦檢察官的欄位 寫的是別人的名字
It's not unusual for the name that's made public to differ.
這沒什麼 檯面上常常會寫別人的名字
But Mr. Datehara was the one really in charge.
不過實際負責指揮的人 的確是伊達原先生
None of the evidence was accepted?
所有證據都沒被採用？
No.
是的
The judge mentioned something about the impact on all citizens.
她說什麼要考量對全體國民的影響
It really is difficult to introduce new evidence during the second instance.
要在第二審提出新證據果然很困難
What did Mr. Akizumi say?
明墨律師的反應呢？
About that…
這個嘛…
What's our next move?
明墨律師，該怎麼辦？
We need more evidence before the next trial.
得在下次開庭前找出其他證據
That's unnecessary.
沒有那個必要
Unnecessary?
沒有必要？
Why?
為什麼？
I don't know.
我也不知道
But his demeanor suggested he has something in mind.
但是他看起來已經有想法了
I'm still trying to figure out Mr. Akizumi's strategy.
雖然我還不清楚明墨律師在想什麼
Maybe I need to broaden my perspective.
也許得用更遠的眼光來審視
In the case with Hiyama,
在緋山的事件中
he uncovered illicit dealings between Prosecutor Himeno and Professor Nakajima.
揭發了姬野檢察官 以及中島教授的違法行為
Then, with Shoichiro, he revealed Tomita's corruption.
在正一郎的事件中 揭發了富田的違法罪行
And in Kurusu's series of rape cases,
在來栖的非合意性交案
he exposed Chief Kurata.
揭發了倉田刑事部長的事
Given Mr. Akizumi's track record,
這樣一來…
his goal this time
本次的目的
might be exposing Mr. Ueda and Kazaki's corruption.
果然是要揭發上田先生 跟加崎的違法行為吧
That seems certain.
那一點無庸置疑
But there could be more to it.
但也許不只如此
Today, I had a chat with someone I studied law with.
我今天問了司法實習的同學
It turns out that Chief Prosecutor Datehara was heading
12年前在千葉地檢負責調查
He handled the Itoi family murders as well.
糸井家滅門案也一樣
After that, he rose to the top at an extraordinary pace.
聽說他後來以非比尋常的速度升遷
Just as I suspected…
果然是這樣
Chief Prosecutor Datehara was involved as well.
伊達原檢事正也是關係人
And one more thing.
還有一件事
Mr. Akizumi frequently visits a dog shelter.
明墨律師常出入狗狗中途之家
There's a dog named Mame there that looks just like Mill.
那裡有一隻名叫小豆的狗 跟米魯長得非常像
And a girl too.
還有一個女孩
A girl?
女孩？
Her name is Saya Makino.
名字是牧野紗耶
She's 17 years old.
年齡為17歲
Saya?
紗耶？
It seems she doesn't talk in front of people she doesn't know.
那個女孩似乎不會在陌生人面前開口
But she seemed happy when talking to Mr. Akizumi.
但她看起來跟明墨律師聊得很開心
They must have known each other for quite some time.
他們大概認識很久了吧
It took me a while to figure out who she was.
我一直猜不透那個女孩到底是誰
But I finally connected the dots.
但我總算明白了
Take a look at this.
你看這個
Mr. Shimizu had an only daughter.
志水先生有一名獨生女
Her name was kept anonymous in the article,
雖然報導中用的是假名
She'd be 17 now.
現在就17歲了
You mean…
那麼…
Ms. Saya is Mr. Shimizu's daughter?
紗耶小姐就是志水先生的女兒？
It's highly likely.
很有可能
I don't know what the connection is between Mr. Akizumi and Mr. Shimizu.
我不清楚明墨律師 和志水先生之間是什麼關係
But Chief Prosecutor Datehara, my father, and Mr. Hiyama…
但伊達原檢事正跟我父親 還有緋山先生
They're all connected to the incident 12 years ago.
全員都跟12年前的事件有關
This isn't a coincidence.
這並不是巧合
Mr. Akizumi's actions seem to revolve around Mr. Shimizu's case.
明墨律師的行動 圍繞著志水先生的事件
But…
但是…
I don't see the connection to the second case with Shoichiro
第二個正一郎事件和這次的事件
and this case yet.
還看不出有什麼關聯
MAKI SAWAHARA
（澤原麻希）
Wait a minute…
難不成…
FORMER COLLEAGUE GETS DEATH SENTENCE IN FAMILY MURDER CASE
（糸井家滅門案 千葉地檢判其前同事死刑）
Mr. Akizumi.
明墨律師
You were still here?
你們還在啊？
I've been thinking.
我們在思考
Why did you…
為什麼你會接下…
take on this case?
這次的事件
To secure an acquittal for Ms. Sawahara.
要幫助澤原小姐獲判無罪
I thought your motive behind this
是因為這個事件的背後有一名政治家
was taking down the politician Tatsuya Kazaki.
我原本以為是因為加崎達也
But that's not it.
但並不是這個原因
I finally understand…
我總算明白了
what you're trying to do.
也瞭解明墨律師想做什麼了
I know…
在這個事件中
who you're targeting in this case.
明墨律師所注視的對手
It's…
那就是…
the person who sentenced Mr. Shimizu to death 12 years ago.
12年前判志水先生死刑的人
Welcome.
歡迎啊
Your companion is waiting for you.
您的熟人在等候
Your aim…
你鎖定的目標是…
was Judge Seko.
瀨古判事
JUDGE NARUMI SEKO
（瀨古成美法官）
There is one person connected to this case and the one with Shoichiro.
跟這次的事件 以及正一郎事件有關的人物
Judge Seko also delivered the guilty verdict
在和正一郎有關的松永先生審判案中
in Mr. Matsunaga's trial linked to Shoichiro.
判他有罪的也是瀨古判事
The accused is sentenced to two years in prison.
判處被告兩年有期徒刑
Wait!
請等一下！
Mr. Matsunaga is innocent!
松永先生是無辜的！
I order him to leave!
命令他立刻退庭！
Mr. Akizumi,
明墨律師
you've been targeting Judge Seko all this time.
你一直看著瀨古判事
That's why you observed Mr. Matsunaga's trial from the gallery.
你之所以在旁聽席看松永先生的審判
And that's why you used Shoichiro's trial to expose Tomita's corruption.
利用正一郎的審判 揭露富田的違法行為的理由
All to reach Judge Seko.
都是為了接近瀨古判事
If my theory is correct,
如果這個推理是正確的
it means Judge Seko is corrupt and needs to be exposed.
就表示瀨古判事 也有你想揭露的黑暗面
Was she already bribed by Tomita then?
她當時已經被富田收買了？
Is that why she found Mr. Matsunaga guilty?
所以松永先生才會被判有罪？
In this trial,
瀨古判事在這次的審判中
Once again,
她又打算操作審判結果
Judge Seko never intended to acquit Ms. Sawahara, who's a hindrance to Kazaki.
瀨古判事打從一開始 就不打算判她無罪
Am I wrong, Mr. Akizumi?
難道我有說錯嗎？明墨律師
Seko's ambition is to become the Supreme Court Justice.
瀨古瞄準的是最高裁判事的位子
To secure this position,
為了實現這個目標
she seeks connections with big political figures.
她需要跟政治界的大人物套好交情
After all, it's the Cabinet that appoints the Supreme Court Justice.
因為最高裁判事是由內閣任命的
Following Tomita's downfall,
富田失勢後
her new ally is Kazaki.
她鎖定了加崎
Just as I thought, Seko presided over the second instance,
就跟我想的一樣，二審法官是瀨古
likely orchestrated by Kazaki to prevent further scrutiny.
為了防止再受到追究 加崎一定在背地裡用了各種手段
What about the GPS tracker?
那定位系統呢？
Before the trial, I went to see Seko.
我在開庭前去見過瀨古
And I hinted at my investigation into Ueda.
暗示她我在調查上田
We have a lead on who might have set her up.
我知道是誰陷害她
We're currently investigating this man.
我正在調查那名男人
We should obtain the evidence we need soon.
馬上就會找到證據了
Ueda was probably oblivious to the tracker
上田剛開始並沒有發現
until Seko reached out through Kazaki.
直到瀨古透過加崎聯絡他為止
I knew it.
果然是這樣
You intentionally made him notice.
你是故意讓他發現的
As a result, Ueda used your shadowing to his advantage,
結果上田反過來指控你跟蹤
and Seko rejected all pieces of evidence.
讓瀨古拒絕採用所有證據
"In this trial,
這次的審判
whether the judge will accept new evidence will play a key part."
最大的關鍵就是法官是否採用新證據
This made their connection evident.
這麼一來那些傢伙的關係 就變得十分清楚
That attorney…
那個律師
He must have been getting away with a lot of unreasonable behavior until now.
即使再亂來，至今都沒有踢過鐵板吧
Just a few days before the public trial, he made contact with me.
他在開庭前幾天還來找我
I could've filed a complaint with the Bar Association.
早知道當時就向律師公會投訴他了
Well,
那真是可惜
you certainly should have done that.
你該那麼做才對
How unusual.
真少見
You seem very cautious of him.
你很戒備他呢
Well…
因為啊
I've seen many people fall prey to him, one after another,
我在那個男人附近 看到大意的人一個個
when caught off guard.
都摔落至谷底
Do you know…
為了爬到這個地位
how much hardship I've endured to reach this position?
你以為我費了多少的苦心？
Your firm words reassure me.
聽到你這麼有自信，我就放心了
However,
不過…
Akizumi is relentless.
明墨很頑強
Don't let him catch you out.
小心不要被他抓到把柄
In other words,
也就是說，這次審判
our only chance of winning this trial is by taking down Seko.
不攻陷瀨古是沒有勝算的
Seko is the target.
目標是瀨古
I'll expose…
我會揭露…
her corruption.
那傢伙的黑暗面
Subtitle translation by: Ai Matsuoka
字幕翻譯：簡妤臻
You're the only one who can help her!
只有你能拯救那個孩子！
I'll tell you everything that happened 12 years ago.
我全都會告訴你 包括12年前發生了什麼事
I have Egoshi's whereabouts.
我找到江越在哪了
I won't let you get away now.
我不會再讓你逃走了
A world built on money and lust is fragile.
用金錢和慾望建立的世界很脆弱
Let's be flexible.
要靈活一點
I promise to win your acquittal this time.
我這次一定會讓你獲判無罪
Let's go.
走吧
You met Chief Prosecutor Datehara, right?
你和伊達原檢事正見過面吧？
What did you discuss?
聊了什麼？
Tell me everything.
請告訴我一切的真相
I will make Seko get what she deserves.
要讓瀨古得到該有的報應
An impeachment trial.
彈劾審判
Strike first before they do.
要搶在對方之前下手
Even if it means risking everything.
即使兩敗俱傷也無妨